AYUSHMAN KHANDELWAL

SKILLS

- · UI/UX
- Figma
- · Adobe XD
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Wireframing
- Research
- Angular
- · HTML & CSS
- C++ Programming
- Javascript
- TypeScript
- · Graphic Design
- Sales and Marketing
- · Planning and strategies
- Customer Relationship Management
- Python

CERTIFICATIONS

Certification in Gamification

Gamification: Motivation Psychology & The art of Engagement Rob Sutcliffe, Sep 2022

Certified Google UI/UX Designer Google, July 2022

TRAINING/COURSES

Search Engine Optimization

University of California, Davis

UI/UX Designer

Google

Communication and debate

British Council, Delhi

Unity Game Dev.

Udemy

Unreal Game Dev. & C++

Sam Pattuzzi, Udemy

HTML & CSS

Jonas Schmedtmann, Udemy

Google Certified UI/UX Designer

📞 +91-9871133963 🜌 ayushmankhandelwal04@gmail.com 💿 New Delhi, IND

@ behance.net/ayushmakhandel/projects

SUMMARY

UX/UI Designer with 2 years of experience in designing new website functionalities and prototyping. Designed my own startup application interface. Have done internships in various areas including UI/UX, CRM, Making a bot, Marketing and SEO. I don't like to stop expanding my horizons and learning new stuff.

EDUCATION

B.Tech, Electronics and Communication Thapar Institute Of Engineering And Technology 2020-2024 Patiala, Punjab

Senior Secondary (XII), Science Modern Vidya Niketan Aravali Hills

2020

Faridabad, Haryana

EXPERIENCE

UX/UI and Front-end Developer Intern Barco NV

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023 Noida-Uttar Pradesh

Barco NV: During my internship, I had the opportunity to work on a captivating software project that expanded my skills and knowledge. The hands-on experience strengthened my technical abilities and provided valuable insights into the software development and web development lifecycle.

Roles: Build a projector web interface for the cinema team using Angular framework and NGRX and do the UI design and do the UX research for the same

User Experience Designer Intern

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022 Remote

Orbiting was by far the most challenging UI/UX project I've done. Such a brilliant idea with a brilliant and ambitious mind behind it. I feel lucky that I was a part of the journey. We went in depth with all the components and parts that UI/UX consists from ideation to research to interviews to wireframing.

Roles: The roles that I had in this job were Research, User Experience, User Interface, Prototyping, Wireframing

Strategy, Design & Process Trainee My Laptop Spares

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022 Nehru Place, Delhi

My Laptop Spares: This was my first onsite internship in which I had to travel everyday from home to office and back. It was very different than I was used to. A really fun and insightful experience in which I had a lot to learn

Roles: The Skills And Roles That I Had In This Job Was User Experience (UX), User Interface Prototyping, Strategic Planning, Making The Website BOT, Growth Strategies, Customer Relationship Management (CRM).

STARTUP

HOMELY

The solution for the craving we have for home cooked food. Cloud kitchens are increasing in this country why not make every home a cloud kitchen and deliver the food cooked in homes by the hands of mothers. No more homestyle food cooked by chefs lets start eating homecooked food. To reduce the wastage of food tie-ups with NGO's and giving more job opportunities to the housewives and helping in fulfilling their dream of having a restaurant or a business.